What type of food is served to
welcome new students at IIT Delhi?  Let's see.
So the first thing I did was get coupons
that would get us some [music] special food.
So first up is Matar Pulao, Then
Dal, Then Kadhai Paneer, Kalakand, Lachha
Paratha, Tandoori Roti and Miss Roti.  And the
main things are still left.  So stay tuned.   Then there
's macaroni and as usual
salad.  Then brother here is pocket pizza which
looks good.  After that,
there is butter chicken for non-vegetarians.  Then papad,
aloo chaat and the best thing is kulfi.
With which our veg thali looks like this and
non-veg thali looks like this.  So if you also want to
eat such good food then you will have to spend in advance.
And you will also have to subscribe to the channel.
So subscribe quickly.  See you
in the next video, bye.